<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://w4xccino.github.io/blog</id>
    <title>My Site Blog</title>
    <updated>2023-10-31T18:05:00.000Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://w4xccino.github.io/blog"/>
    <subtitle>My Site Blog</subtitle>
    <icon>https://w4xccino.github.io/img/favicon.ico</icon>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Today is Halloween]]></title>
        <id>https://w4xccino.github.io/blog/halloween</id>
        <link href="https://w4xccino.github.io/blog/halloween"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T18:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uhmm I started to regret about not have gone to my English Classes today. I mean, this is my favorite date in the whole year and I'm here, in front of my screen, typing like a fucking loser. My GF has gone to France and she's is probably sleeping already.]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Uhmm I started to regret about not have gone to my English Classes today. I mean, this is my favorite date in the whole year and I'm here, in front of my screen, typing like a fucking loser. My GF has gone to France and she's is probably sleeping already. </p><p>I don't know how to feel about myself. Am I a loser? Maybe just because I didn't go to my English classes I would lose the best day of the year? Should I feel like this? Probably I'll tell to my sister that I went to ELC but... IDK. I would like to play something to get those thoughts out of my mind but there's no one to play with...
So I'm here... without money, without friends, losing Halloween, but with an insane blog where to put all my feelings.
I was thinking about sharing it... but probably I won't do it.</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Billy Toledo</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/w4xccino</uri>
        </author>
        <category label="thoughts" term="thoughts"/>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome To My Shit]]></title>
        <id>https://w4xccino.github.io/blog/welcome</id>
        <link href="https://w4xccino.github.io/blog/welcome"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T17:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone, I know this is kinda cliche for most of you. But I think the idea of make my own blog, with my own tools(but this is docusaurus) makes me feel so productive and pure. I need to be honest with myself starting to say I didn't go to my English Classes because I was doing this shit. I mean, it's not a shit itself, I really proud of this because It was sort of challenging for me. Specially the part of Deployment.]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hi everyone, I know this is kinda cliche for most of you. But I think the idea of make my own blog, with my own tools(but this is docusaurus) makes me feel so productive and pure. I need to be honest with myself starting to say I didn't go to my English Classes because I was doing this shit. I mean, it's not a shit itself, I really proud of this because It was sort of challenging for me. Specially the part of <code>Deployment</code>.</p><p>I followed a Youtube video and documentation as well. But I think tomorrow I'll link this, which is on GitHub Pages with my new web domain!!</p><blockquote><p><a href="https://billynotes.online" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">https://billynotes.online</a></p></blockquote><p>Actually, I'd to create another blog using Org Mode Syntax. Currently, I don't know how to insert music here in order to put it sometimes further in the future.</p><p><img loading="lazy" src="https://cdn.betterttv.net/emote/5b6c5efadd8fb0185163bd4f/3x.webp" alt="BoneZone" class="img_ev3q"></p><p>Tomorrow, I'll add some documentation and guides that I would learn about DevOps and all that kind of crap where I really got into it. OMG!</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Billy Toledo</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/w4xccino</uri>
        </author>
        <category label="welcome" term="welcome"/>
        <category label="thoughts" term="thoughts"/>
    </entry>
</feed>